kungfucinema.com 2006-06-19

# Privacy Statement

**PRIVACY STATEMENT**

**Contents**

Introduction  >

Affiliates  >

Forums  >

Promotions  >

Store  >

Tracking  >

|   | 

**Introduction**

Kung Fu Cinema is committed to protecting the privacy of its visitors. Any contact information provided to us remains confidential and is not shared with any other party unless authorized to do so. All monetary transactions take place on secure, third-party sites.

**Affiliates**

Kung Fu Cinema has partnered with a number of reputable businesses such as [HKFlix.com](http://www.hkflix.com/xq/asp/aid.006349/qx/ahome.htm) in order to provide our readers with easy access to their products and services. To the best of our knowledge, all of our affiliates use safe and secure procedures to process orders online. If it becomes known to us that any affiliate is violating consumer trust we will investigate the issue and may sever ties with the company. To report a violation to us, please send us an [e-mail](mailto:mpollard@kungfucinema.com). 

**Forums**

The Kung Fu Cinema forums, also known as [Kung Fu Fandom](http://pub3.ezboard.com/bkungfufandom), operate on an independent server provided by [ezboard](http://www.ezboard.com/) (see their [privacy statement](http://www.ezboard.com/corporate/legal_privacypolicy.html)). Users are required to register with ezboard. This information is not made available to the Kung Fu Fandom administrator or any moderators. IP addresses, which identify individual computer connections to the Internet are viewable by the forum administrator and may be used only to ban users who violate forum policies. We are not responsible for any private information that is posted on the forums by users. To protect yourself, it is recommended that you do not share home addresses, phone numbers, or any other personal information on our forums. Any user who maliciously posts any personal information about another user without their consent will be banned.

**Promotions**

We collect e-mail addresses and names during contest promotions for the sole purpose of randomly selecting winners. Winners will receive their prizes by providing mailing addresses and phone numbers. Once the contest is completed, all contact information for contestants and winners is deleted. None of this information is shared with any other party.

**Store**

The Kung Fu Cinema Store sells merchandise exclusively through [PayPal](http://www.paypal.com/), a money exchange site verified by both [TRUSTe](https://www.truste.org/validate.php?invnum=4023&fromcgi=1) and [BBBOnLine](http://www.bbbonline.org/cks.asp?id=20111061155818568). Users are required to register with PayPal and set up an account to purchase goods from us. Once a transaction takes place, only a name, a mailing address, an e-mail address, and any other information that a users wishes to share is provided to us. This information is used solely to mail out merchandise or contact the buyer concerning their purchase and is not shared with any other party.

**Tracking**

We use traffic tracking and statistics scripts provided by [Aplus.net](http://www.aplus.net/), [theCounter.com](http://www.thecounter.com/), and [AddFreeStats.com](http://www.addfreestats.com/) to monitor site traffic. These services can in some cases, view general public information about a visitor's computer including IP addresses, operating system, browser, and where a visitor linked from to arrive at our site. However, the visitor remains anonymous as these scripts do not track any personal information about the computer user.
